Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
8094
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-
600 cubic feet.
Vinyl records and other A/V Recordings, Financial Records, Manuscripts, Memorabilia, Photocopies, Photographs, Printed Materials, Publications.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Afrika Bambaataa is an American disc jockey, singer, and songwriter from the South Bronx, New York. Often called the “Godfather” of Hip Hop, Bambaataa has helped to define Hip Hop since it emerged in the South Bronx in the 1970s. One of a handful of Hip Hop's 1970s originators, Bambaataa gave Hip Hop its name, and was the first to define its core artistic elements - DJing, rapping, break dancing, and graffiti art - under one cultural umbrella. His cultural organization, the Universal Zulu Nation, has helped to spread Hip Hop culture throughout the world. His genre-defining 1982 song "Planet Rock" and subsequent electro-funk tracks have become icons of hip-hop and electronic music. In 2007 he was nominated for induction into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-; Universal Zulu Nation (Organization)
Subjects:
African American youth -- Social life and customs.; Disc jockeys.; Electronic music.; Funk (Music).; Hip-hop.; Hip-hop -- Influence.; Hip-hop -- History. -- United States; Music -- Social aspects.; Race relations.; Rap (Music); Rap (Music) -- Political aspects.; Rap musicians.; Hip-hop -- New York.; Rap (Music) -- New York.; Hip-hop; Rap (Music); Rap musicians; Social history
Places:
Bronx (New York, N.Y.) -- Social conditions -- 20th century.; New York (State) -- New York; New York (State) -- Bronx; United States
Form and Genre Terms:
History
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to collection restricted until completion of processing, with the exception of vinyl records that have been individually cataloged.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Manuscripts
a. School Papers and Assignments
b. Africa Trip
c. Soul Scrapbooks and Music Writing
d. Notebooks and Miscellaneous Manuscripts
e. Lyrics and Poems
f. Bronx River Neighborhood Center
g. Phone and Contact Lists
Series II. Flyers
Series III. Photographs
Series IV. Personal Papers
a. Personal Papers
b. Press About Bambaataa
c. Catalogs and Mail
Series V. Universal Zulu Nation Documents
a. Infinity Lessons
b. Administration
Series VI. Stage Costumes and Clothing
Series VII. Periodicals and Publications
a. Small Press Publications
b. Periodicals
c. Publications from 3410 De Reimer Ave. Bronx, NY
d. Other Publications
Series VIII. Moving images and audio recordings
a. Video cassettes
a. Audio cassettes
Series IX. Music collection
12 inch vinyl
Sureshots and altered/obscured
Numbered by Bambaataa
Annotated, not numbered (Alphabetical by artist)
A-D
E-H
I-L
L-O
P-S
T-Z
Numbers, unknown and various
Second alpha sequence
Cataloged individually
Not annotated (Alphabetical by artist)
A
B
C
D
E
F
G
H
I
J
K
L
M
N
O
P
Q
R
S
Afrika Bambaataa recordings
Renegades of Rhythm Tour
Test pressings and white labels (not yet cataloged)
Compilations (not yet cataloged)
7 inch vinyl
Numbered (not yet cataloged)
Annotated not numbered (not yet cataloged)
No annotations (not yet cataloged)
Acetates and lacquer discs
Cassettes (not yet cataloged)
CDs (not yet cataloged)
Series X. Ephemera
CONTAINER LIST
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      Series contains vinyl discs that are either not annotated or the annotations are small and were missed during the sorting of discs. While some effort was taken to bring together piences that were dense in copy-specific track preferences. These items are arranged in alphabetical order by artists’ last name or the name of the group. Each letter of the alphabet has a subseries. Compilations, soundtracks, and other albums with various artists are in subseries together. Artists and groups whose names start with a number are in a separate subseries. Most artists are alphabetized under the name they are most well-known as (e.g. Puff Daddy; Prince; Fela). The variations of names are contained in the Creator field. In a few cases, however, artists’ aliases were unknown, and they may have been listed under two different artist names.
      - B
        - B-52's - Summer of love, 1986; SR-11421; B-52's (Box 178)
          Catalog # 0-20509; A-side Matrix # 0-20509 ASHI 0 13-24542 SHI
          Warner Bros. Records
          Burbank, California
        - B-52's - Mesopotamia, 1982; SR-11422; B-52's; Byrne, David (Box 178)
          Catalog # MINI 3641; A-side Matrix # MINI-1-3641-LW1
        - B Angie B - I don't want to lose your love, 1991; SR-11020; B Angie B (Box 178)
          Catalog # V-15656; A-side Matrix # V-1-15656-Z1
          Capitol Records
          Hollywood, California
        - B Angie B - Sweet thang, 1991; SR-11021; B Angie B (Box 178)
          Catalog # V-15759; A-side Matrix # V-1-15759-Z1
        - B Beat Girls - Jungle swing, 1983; SR-11022; B Beat Girls (Box 178)
          In same jacket as # SR-11023. 2 copies
          Catalog # TFW 1008AS; A-side Matrix # TFW 1008 AS
          25 West Records
          New York, New York
        - B Beat Girls - Jungle swing, 1983; SR-11023; B Beat Girls (Box 178)
          In same jacket as # SR-11022. 2 copies
        - B-Boy 3000 - When heroes die EP (Disc one), 1999; SR-11024; B-Boy 3000 (Box 178)
          In same jacket as # SR-11025. Double album
          Catalog # MICTLAN 0003; A-side Matrix # L-51901
          Mictlan
          Los Angeles, California
        - B-Boy 3000 - When heroes die EP (Disc two), 1999; SR-11025; B-Boy 3000 (Box 178)
          In same jacket as # SR-11024. Double album
        - B Boys - Rock the house; Cuttin' Herbie, 1983; SR-11026; B Boys (Box 178)
          Catalog # VTI-002; A-side Matrix # VTI-002
          Vintertainment
        - B. Brown Posse - Drop it on the one, 1993; SR-11423; B. Brown Posse (Box 178)
          Catalog # MCA12-54631; A-side Matrix # MCA 11627 FDS-2
          MCA Records, Inc.
          Universal City, California
        - B-Fats - The B-Fats, 1987; SR-11424; B-Fats (Box 178)
          Annotated
          Catalog # RT 005; A-side Matrix # RT-005-A
          Rooftop Records
        - B-Legit - Check it out; Gotta buy your dope from us, 1996; SR-11425; B-Legit; E-40; Kurupt (Box 178)
          Catalog # JDAB-42417-1; A-side Matrix # JDAB-42417-1-A-1
          Jive
        - B-Legit - Ghetto smile, 1996; SR-11426; B-Legit; Hall, Daryl (Box 178)
          Catalog # JDCD-42400-1; A-side Matrix # JDCD-42400-1-C1
        - B-Movie - Nowhere girl, 1982; SR-11427; B-Movie (Box 178)
          Catalog # BZZ X8; A-side Matrix # BZZX8 B/1 B//1 420 V
          Some Bizarre
          London, United Kingdom
        - B-Movie - Nowhere girl, 1982; SR-11428; B-Movie (Box 178)
          Catalog # PVC 4903; A-side Matrix # PVC-4903-A
          PVC Records
          South Plainfield, New Jersey
        - B Real - Hit 'em high (The monstars' anthem), 1996; SR-11429; B Real; Busta Rhymes; Coolio; LL Cool J; Method Man (Box 178)
          Catalog # DMD 2329; A-side Matrix # ST DM 85CC8-85009 1 A
          Atlantic
        - B-Side - So hot; Cairo, 1985; SR-11027; B-Side (Box 178)
          Catalog # CEL 178; A-side Matrix # CEL 178-A
          Celluloid
        - B-Side - So hot; Cairo, 1985; SR-11430; B-Side (Box 178)
        - B-Side - So hot; Cairo, 1985; SR-11431; B-Side (Box 178)
        - B-Tribe - You won't see me cry, 1993; SR-11432; B-Tribe (Box 178)
          Catalog # 0-85657; A-side Matrix # STDM-71403-71404-71405-1
        - B-Zet - Everlasting pictures (Right through infinity) (Disc One), 1995; SR-11433; B-Zet; Darlesia (Box 178)
          In same jacket as # SR-11434. Double album. Annotated
          Catalog # SAM 1615; A-side Matrix # SAM 1615 A1
          Eye Q
          Germany
        - B-Zet - Everlasting pictures (Right through infinity) (Disc Two), 1995; SR-11434; B-Zet; Darlesia (Box 178)
          In same jacket as # SR-11433. Double album. Annotated
          Catalog # SAM 1615; A-side Matrix # SAM 1615 C1
        - B2K - Uh huh (Badboys Remix), 2002; SR-11435; B2K; G-Dep (Box 178)
          Catalog # EAS 56747; A-side Matrix # XSS 56747A-1A
          Epic
        - B2K - Gots ta be, 2002; SR-11436; B2K (Box 178)
          Catalog # EAS 56730; A-side Matrix # XSS 56730 A-1B
        - B2K - Uh huh pt. 2, 2001; SR-11437; B2K; Nazkar (Box 178)
          Catalog # EAS 54818; A-side Matrix # XSS 54818-A-1B
        - B5 - U got me, 2005; SR-11438; B5 (Box 178)
          Catalog # PR 301801; A-side Matrix # ST-PR-301801A-1
          Bad Boy Entertainment
        - Qwy Ba' Ba' - Throw up your hoodies, 1995; SR-11028; Qwy Ba' Ba'; L' Anka' Ba' Ba'; Shamar Da Boonkie (Box 178)
          Catalog # RB12345; A-side Matrix # RB-12345-A
          Fresh Start Records
          Jamaica, New York
        - B.A.B.B. - Wack Wack Apple Jack, 1986; SR-11029; B.A.B.B. (Box 178)
          In same jacket as # SR-11030. 2 copies. Annotated
          Catalog # BAR 06; A-side Matrix # BAR-06-A
          Big Apple Records
        - B.A.B.B. - Wack Wack Apple Jack, 1986; SR-11030; B.A.B.B. (Box 178)
          In same jacket as # SR-11029. 2 copies
        - Babble - Beautiful; Tribe, 1993; SR-11031; Babble; Q. Tee (Box 178)
          Catalog # 0-40972; A-side Matrix # 040972 A SR1
          Reprise Records
        - Babes in Toyland - We are family, 1995; SR-11032; Babes in Toyland (Box 178)
          Catalog # 0-43553; A-side Matrix # 0-43553 A 5122
        - Babie and Keyes - Secrets of love, 1988; SR-11033; Babie and Keyes (Box 178)
          Catalog # CR12030; A-side Matrix # C1212-030-A
          Criminal Records
        - Babie and Keyes - Playgirl, 1987; SR-11034; Babie and Keyes (Box 178)
          Catalog # CRIM 00011; A-side Matrix # CRIM 10011 A
        - Babie and Keyes - Playgirl, 1987; SR-11035; Babie and Keyes (Box 178)
        - Babie and Keyes - Playgirl, 1987; SR-11036; Babie and Keyes (Box 178)
        - Babla and Kanchan - Karajwa me lage, 1996; SR-11037; Babla and Kanchan (Box 178)
          Catalog # JMC-1121; A-side Matrix # JMC 1121-A
          Jamaican Me Crazy
          Richmond Hill, New York
        - Baby Brother - Baby brother, 1981; SR-11038; Baby Brother (Box 178)
          Catalog # SD 5225; A-side Matrix # ST-CTN-814737-A
          Cotillion
        - Baby D - Get your hustle on, 1998; SR-11039; Baby D; Too $hort (Box 178)
          Catalog # JDAB-46601-1; A-side Matrix # JDAB-46601-1-A1
          $hort Records
        - Baby Namboos - Hard times, 2000; SR-11040; Baby Namboos (Box 178)
          Catalog # PP12 7030-1; A-side Matrix # PP12 7030-1A
          Palm Pictures
        - Baby'O - In the forest, 1980; SR-11041; Baby'O (Box 178)
          Catalog # BO-10003; A-side Matrix # 1000-3A
          Baby'O Music Enterprises
          United States
        - Baby S - I'm ghetto, 2001; SR-11042; Baby S (Box 178)
          Catalog # EAS 16964; A-side Matrix # XSS-16964-A-2A
          Ruthless Records
        - Baby S - Street Fractions (Disc one), 2002; SR-11043; Baby S (Box 178)
          In same jacket as # SR-11044. Double album
          Catalog # E2S 56785; A-side Matrix # XSS-56786-1A
        - Baby S - Street Fractions (Disc two), 2002; SR-11044; Baby S (Box 178)
          In same jacket as # SR-11043. Double album
        - Baby Wayne - Mama; Ho Lord, 1991; SR-11439; Baby Wayne; Ranks, Nardo (Box 178)
          Catalog # VPRD 854; A-side Matrix # VPRD 854AA
          Pickout
        - Babyboy - Mix one labs 5, 1996; SR-11440; Babyboy; Ilike (Box 178)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # Mix1labs-A
          Mix one labs
        - Babyface - This is for the lover in you, 1996; SR-11045; Babyface (Box 178)
          In same jacket as # SR-11046. 2 copies
          Catalog # EAS 8668; A-side Matrix # XSS 8668 1A
        - Babyface - This is for the lover in you, 1996; SR-11046; Babyface (Box 178)
          In same jacket as # SR-11045. 2 copies
        - Babyface - Mary Mack, 1987; SR-11047; Babyface (Box 178)
          Catalog # V-71159; A-side Matrix # V-1-77159
          Solar
        - Bacharach, Burt - Casino Royale, 1967; SR-11048; Bacharach, Burt; Herb Alpert & the Tijuana Brass; Springfield, Rusty (Box 178)
          Catalog # COSO-5005; A-side Matrix # UZRS--4046--3S
          Colgems
        - Bacharach, Burt - Reach out, 1967; SR-11049; Bacharach, Burt (Box 178)
          Catalog # SP 4131; A-side Matrix # A&M SP 4161(RE-1)-15
          A&M Records
          Canada
        - Backbone - Five, deuce, four, tre, 2000; SR-11050; Backbone; Backbone AKA "Mr. Fat Face 100" (Box 179)
          Catalog # UNIR 20361-1; A-side Matrix # UNIR-20361-1A
          Universal Records
        - Backbone - Five, deuce, four, tre, 2000; SR-11051; Backbone; Backbone AKA "Mr. Fat Face 100" (Box 179)
        - Backbone - Five, deuce, four, tre, 2000; SR-11052; Backbone; Backbone AKA "Mr. Fat Face 100" (Box 179)
        - Backintyme - Backintyme, 1995; SR-11053; Backintyme (Box 179)
          Catalog # DIG 033-1; A-side Matrix # DIG-033-1A
          Dig It International
        - Backstreet Boys - Get down (you're the one for me), 1996; SR-11054; Backstreet Boys (Box 179)
          Catalog # JIVE T 394 P; A-side Matrix # JIVET394P A-1
        - Backstreet Boys - Everybody (Backstreet's back), 1998; SR-11055; Backstreet Boys (Box 179)
          Catalog # 01241-42515-1; A-side Matrix # 01241-42515-1A
        - Backyard Band - Hood related (Disc one), 1997; SR-11056; Backyard Band (Box 179)
          In same jacket as # SR-11057. Double album
          Catalog # PA1025-1; A-side Matrix # PA-1025-1-A
          Future Records and Tapes
          Landover, Maryland
        - Backyard Band - Hood related (Disc two), 1997; SR-11057; Backyard Band (Box 179)
          In same jacket as # SR-11056. Double album. Annotated
          Catalog # PA1025-1; A-side Matrix # PA-1025-1-C
        - Backyard Band - Hood related (Disc one), 1997; SR-11058; Backyard Band (Box 179)
          In same jacket as # SR-11059. Double album
          Catalog # PA1025-1; A-side Matrix # PA-1025-1-E
        - Backyard Band - Hood related (Disc two), 1997; SR-11059; Backyard Band (Box 179)
          In same jacket as # SR-11058. Double album. Annotated
          Catalog # PA1025-1; A-side Matrix # PA-1025-1-G
        - Backyard Band - We like it raw (Disc one), 1995; SR-11060; Backyard Band (Box 179)
          In same jacket as # SR-11061. Double album
          Catalog # PA1019; A-side Matrix # PA-1019-1-A
        - Backyard Band - We like it raw (Disc two), 1995; SR-11061; Backyard Band (Box 179)
          In same jacket as # SR-11060. Double album
          Catalog # PA1019; A-side Matrix # PA-1019-1-E
        - Backyard Band - We like it raw (Disc one), 1995; SR-11062; Backyard Band (Box 179)
          In same jacket as # SR-11063. Double album
        - Backyard Band - We like it raw (Disc two), 1995; SR-11063; Backyard Band (Box 179)
          In same jacket as # SR-11062. Double album
        - Backyard Band - The dippa, 2001; SR-11064; Backyard Band (Box 179)
          In same jacket as # SR-11065. 2 copies
          Catalog # BY-100; A-side Matrix # STOCK BY100 A
          Unknown
        - Backyard Band - The dippa, 2001; SR-11065; Backyard Band (Box 179)
          In same jacket as # SR-11064. 2 copies
        - Bad Azz - Murderous MC's, 2000; SR-11066; Bad Azz (Box 179)
          Catalog # SPRO 81345; A-side Matrix # 81345-13-A
          Priority Records
        - Bad Azz - Ghetto star, 1999; SR-11067; Bad Azz (Box 179)
          Catalog # SPRO 81163; A-side Matrix # SPRO-81163-A/B
        - Bad Bascomb Band - Do it twice, 1976; SR-11068; Bad Bascomb Band; Romer, Max (Box 179)
          Catalog # SP 143; A-side Matrix # F4RS-2548-A1-1-1
          Spectrum Records
        - Bad Boy Orchestra - Bomba, 1995; SR-11069; Bad Boy Orchestra (Box 179)
          Catalog # STR-101; A-side Matrix # STR-101-A
          Sneak Tip Records
        - Bad Boys - Bad Boys, 1985; SR-11070; Bad Boys; K Love (Box 179)
          Catalog # B6000; A-side Matrix # B-6000-A
          Starlite
        - Bad Bwoy Beatz - Let's dance, 2000; SR-11071; Bad Bwoy Beatz (Box 179)
          Catalog # BBB-3; A-side Matrix # BBB-3-H1
        - Bad Boy's Da Band - Too hot for TV (Disc one), 2003; SR-11281; Bad Boy's Da Band (Box 179)
          In same jacket as # SR-11282. Double album
          Catalog # UNIF 21080-1; A-side Matrix # UNIF-21080-1LP1A
        - Bad Boy's Da Band - Too hot for TV (Disc two), 2003; SR-11282; Bad Boy's Da Band (Box 179)
          In same jacket as # SR-11281. Double album
          Catalog # UNIF 21080-1; A-side Matrix # UNIF-21080-1LP2A
        - Bad Girls - Too through, 1981; SR-11283; Bad Girls (Box 179)
          Catalog # BC4011; A-side Matrix # BC-4011-A
          BC Records
        - Bacharach, Burt - Burt Bacharach's Greatest Hits, 1973; SR-11284; Bacharach, Burt (Box 179)
          Catalog # SP-3661; A-side Matrix # AM SP 33725 P2
          Santa Monica, California
        - Bad Manners - Forging ahead, 1982; SR-11285; Bad Manners (Box 179)
          Catalog # MAGL 5050; A-side Matrix # MAGL-5050-A-1
          Magnet Records
        - Bad Mutha Goose and the Bros Grimm - Be somebody, 1987; SR-11286; Bad Mutha Goose and the Bros Grimm (Box 179)
          Catalog # FR-41188; A-side Matrix # FR 41188 A1
          Fable Records
          Austin, Texas
        - Badarou, Wally - Chief inspector; Novela das nove, 1984; SR-11287; Badarou, Wally (Box 179)
          Catalog # DMD 913; A-side Matrix # STDM-48931-489 86-1
          Island Records
        - Badarou, Wally - Spider woman, 1986; SR-11288; Badarou, Wally (Box 179)
          Catalog # DMD 944; A-side Matrix # STDM-49603-3
        - Badarou, Wally - Hi-life, 1986; SR-11289; Badarou, Wally (Box 179)
          Catalog # DMD 983; A-side Matrix # STDM-50525-4
        - Badarou, Wally - Hi-life, 1986; SR-11290; Badarou, Wally (Box 179)
        - Badd Girls - Cupid stuck (it was just my turn), 1986; SR-11291; Badd Girls (Box 179)
          Catalog # VAR 1986-1; A-side Matrix # VAR-1986-1-A
          VAP Records, Inc
          Amityville, New York
        - Badea, Tony - Da Boomster EP, 1996; SR-11292; Badea, Tony; Tony "Boom Boom" Badea (Box 179)
          Catalog # MP045; A-side Matrix # MP045A
          Music Plant
          Chicago, Illinois
        - Badenough, Boris - Hey Rocky!, 1986; SR-11293; Badenough, Boris (Box 179)
          Catalog # TX130; A-side Matrix # TX-130-A
          Trax Records
        - Badfellas - Soc it to me, 2002; SR-11294; Badfellas; C.K. (Box 179)
          Catalog # N212001; A-side Matrix # N2-12-001-A
          N2
        - Badfinger - Magic Christian music, 1970; SR-11295; Badfinger (Box 179)
          Catalog # ST-3364; A-side Matrix # ST-1-3364-Z3
          Apple Records
        - Badmarsh + Shri - Air I breathe, 1998; SR-11296; Badmarsh + Shri (Box 179)
          Catalog # TB245; A-side Matrix # TB-0245-A RE-1
          Outcaste Records
        - Badu, Erykah - On & on, 1996; SR-11297; Badu, Erykah (Box 179)
          Catalog # U8P 1075; A-side Matrix # U8P-1075A
        - Badu, Erykah - Worldwide undergound, 2003; SR-11298; Badu, Erykah (Box 179)
          Catalog # B0000739-01; A-side Matrix # B000073901-A
          Motown
        - Baha Men - Who let the dogs out, 2000; SR-11299; Baha Men (Box 179)
          Catalog # 51000-1; A-side Matrix # 807-315-1000-1-8A
          S-Curve Records
        - Baha Men - Back to the island, 1992; SR-11300; Baha Men (Box 179)
          Catalog # 0-10061; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-62755-62753-1
          Big Beat
        - Bahamadia - Biggest part of me; Paper thin, 1996; SR-11301; Bahamadia (Box 179)
          Catalog # SPRO-11625; A-side Matrix # SPRO-11625-A
          Chrysalis
        - Bahamadia - Unknowhowwedu, 1995; SR-11302; Bahamadia (Box 179)
          Catalog # SPRO-10447; A-side Matrix # SPRO-10447-A
        - Bahamadia - I confess (Remix), 1996; SR-11303; Bahamadia (Box 179)
          Catalog # SPRO-11622; A-side Matrix # SPRO-11622-A
        - Bahamadia - I confess, 1996; SR-11304; Bahamadia (Box 179)
          Catalog # Y-58437; A-side Matrix # Y-72438-58437-1-6-A1-RE-1
        - Bahamadia - I confess, 1996; SR-11305; Bahamadia (Box 179)
          Catalog # Y-58437; A-side Matrix # Y-72438-58437-1-6-A1-RE1
        - Bahamadia - Unknowhowwedu, 1995; SR-11306; Bahamadia (Box 179)
        - Bahamadia - I confess (Remix), 1996; SR-11307; Bahamadia (Box 179)
        - Bahamadia - I confess, 1996; SR-11308; Bahamadia (Box 179)
          Catalog # SPRO-10492; A-side Matrix # SPRO-10492-A
        - Bahamadia - Kollage (Disc one), 1996; SR-11309; Bahamadia (Box 180)
          In same jacket as # SR-11310. Double album
          Catalog # SPRO-10478; A-side Matrix # SPRO-10478-A
        - Bahamadia - Kollage (Disc two), 1996; SR-11310; Bahamadia (Box 180)
          In same jacket as # SR-11309. Double album
          Catalog # SPRO-10478; A-side Matrix # SPRO-10478-C
        - Baha Men - Back to the island, 1992; SR-11311; Baha Men (Box 180)
        - Bahamut - Final bump, SR-11312; Bahamut (Box 180)
          Catalog # LBS009; A-side Matrix # LBS009A
          Insomniac Records
          Miami, Florida
        - Bahia Black - Capitão do asfalto, 1993; SR-11313; Bahia Black (Box 180)
          In same jacket as # SR-11314. 2 copies
          Catalog # 12 AXM 3; A-side Matrix # DFI 93 7 12 AXM 3 A1
          Axiom
        - Bahia Black - Capitão do asfalto, 1993; SR-11314; Bahia Black (Box 180)
          In same jacket as # SR-11313. 2 copies
        - Bailey, Philip - State of the heart, 1986; SR-11315; Bailey, Philip (Box 180)
          Catalog # 44-05372; A-side Matrix # XSS-175050-1A
          Columbia
        - Bailey, Shah - Get to know me, SR-11316; Bailey, Shah (Box 180)
          Catalog # None; A-side Matrix # UNIQ 2000A LC3008 A
          Synegee Records
        - Bailey, Shah - Get to know me, SR-11317; Bailey, Shah (Box 180)
        - Bailey, Sharon - Cosmic dust, 1981; SR-11318; Bailey, Sharon (Box 180)
          Catalog # SG 347; A-side Matrix # SG-347-A-1
          Salsoul Records
        - Bainbridge, Merril - Mouth, 1996; SR-11319; Bainbridge, Merril (Box 180)
          Catalog # U12 56023; A-side Matrix # U12-56023-A
        - Bak2bassiks - I can feel desire, 1994; SR-11320; Bak2bassiks; Mona Lisa (Box 180)
          Catalog # MCA12 55059; A-side Matrix # MCA 12300
          MCA Records
        - Baker, Anita - Giving you the best that I got, 1988; SR-11321; Baker, Anita (Box 180)
          Catalog # ED 5331; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-5331A-1
          Elektra
        - Baker, Anita - Rapture, 1986; SR-11322; Baker, Anita (Box 180)
          In jacket and sleeve of "Giving you the best that I got"
          Catalog # 60444-1; A-side Matrix # STE-60444-A-1
        - Baker, Anita - Giving you the best that I got, 1988; SR-11323; Baker, Anita (Box 180)
          Catalog # 60827-1; A-side Matrix # ST-E-60827-A-1
        - Baker, Anita - No one in the world, 1986; SR-11324; Baker, Anita (Box 180)